mmanews.com 2013-12-19

# Privacy Policy - MMA News

Updated: July 2, 2013

### MMANews.com Privacy Policy

PLEASE NOTE: OUR PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME. PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES AS YOUR USE OF MMANEWS.COM IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

MMANews.comTM  (the “Company,” “we” or “us”).  We have created this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the very important issue of customer information privacy. The following Privacy Policy discloses our personal information gathering and sharing practices with respect to our website located at [www.MMANews.com](http://www.mmanews.com/) (the “Website”). We will not sell, share or rent your personal information to others in ways other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third party for direct marketing purposes, please e-mail us by using our [contact page](http://www.mmanews.com/contact-us/). Please be advised, however, where California residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from the Company in accordance with the law.

### Use of IP Address

We use your network (IP) address to help prevent security breaches on the site, block users submitting inappropriate content, diagnose problems with our server and to administer the services (“Services”) offered at the Website. We may use your IP address to verify your identity internally or with a third party, but we will never utilize it to send any IP-based advertising to you. Your IP address is recorded so that we can offer the best possible customer service to you at all times.

### Cookies & Web Bugs

We currently employ cookie and web bug technology to associate certain Internet-related habits of visitors to the Website with information that we have in our database. Additionally, we may use other new and evolving sources of information gathering technology in the future (together, “Technology Information”). A “cookie” is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of your computer that allows us to identify you with corresponding data on file in our database or the database of a third-party service provider. Individuals that use the Website must accept cookies in order to access all of the features and functionality available through use of the Website. No personally identifiable information is gathered by the cookie. To find out more information about cookies, including how to disable them, please visit www.cookiecentral.com. A “web bug” consists of source code embedded in an html e-mail or web page that can be used to transfer an individual’s unique user identification to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information on that individual that resides in a database. Use of web bugs allows us to track certain websites that an individual may visit online. Web bugs are also used to assist in ascertaining the products and services that individuals are interested in and to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes. In addition to using web bugs on web pages, we also use web bugs in connection with e-mail messages sent to individuals listed in our database. By visiting the Website, you agree to allow us to share such Website usage with third parties. You may erase and/or disable web bug functionality by following the instructions contained in your browser.

### Personal Information We Collect

We provide membership-based Services. We collect personal information when you register for a membership at the Website. In particular, and without limitation, we collect your first name, last name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number (collectively, “Registration Data”) during the registration process. All visitors to the Website may browse selected portions of the Website and obtain information about our Services without entering any personal information.

### Sharing of Personal Information

Any personal information that you submit to us at the Website remains your property. However, by submitting that information on the Website, you grant to us the right to use your personal information for any legal purpose. In addition, you agree that we may contact you with updates and/or any other information that we may deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with the Services.

We reserve the right to release current or past user information in the event that: a) we believe that the Website is being or has been used in violation of the Terms and Conditions and/or to commit unlawful acts; b) where such disclosure is required by law and/or where we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order and/or subpoena; or c) if we and/or the Company are sold or acquired. Moreover, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when the Company, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time-to-time.

### Aggregate Information

We reserve the right to transfer and/or sell aggregate or group data about our users for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage and/or other characteristics of our users as a group without disclosing personally identifiable information. By submitting your personal information to, and/or using, the Website, you agree to allow us to transfer and/or sell such aggregate data to third parties.

### Third Party Websites

We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of the third party advertisers featured on the Website. The entities that advertise and/or place banner ads on the Website are independent third parties and are not affiliated with the Company.

### Minors

We do not knowingly solicit or collect information from visitors under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, you are not permitted to use, and/or submit your personal information at, the Website. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information from a minor, the information will be immediately deleted from our database. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

### Security

We store your personal information in a technically secure environment. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of such information, we employ appropriate industry standard procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewall, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, SSL encryption, monitoring technology and adaptive analysis of network traffic. However, no data transmitted over the Internet can be 100% secure. Accordingly, while we endeavor to protect the security of your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any personal information that you transmit to us over the Internet and, as such, you assume the risk of transmitting such information to us. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage and to engage in remedial measures.

### Your Acceptance of This Privacy Policy

By using the Website and/or agreeing to receive information via e-mail from us, you agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Website. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Website and/or acceptance of our e-mail communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Website, please contact us at http://www.mmanews.com/contact-us/.
